ALPHA

Information

Units

Armada

CORTEX

Cortex

Development

DONATE

BAR servers can be unstable at times. A problem with our server-host is identified and we're waiting for it get fixed.

Privacy policy
==============

BAR
===

### Website

#### beyondallreason.info

On this website we only use Google Analytics and anonymized IP-addresses, so we can only see how people are using the website. We also disabled tracking for all YouTube video-content that is visible on this website. Visiting our website will not store or track any personal data.

We do offer live-battles which show players in servers with their chosen nickname from their BAR-player-account. Games played online are also stored as downloadable replays.

If you wish to donate through our Paypal integration, then the [Paypal Privacy policy](https://www.paypal.com/webapps/mpp/ua/privacy-full) will apply there.

‍

### BAR lobby server

#### server\*.beyondallreason.info

The Statement of Privacy below applies to the official Beyond All Reason (BAR) lobby server as hosted under https://server\*.beyondallreason.info. Under the GDPR, we're required to notify you about the legal basis on which we process User Personal Information. When registering an account or playing Beyond All Reason, some identifying information is stored on the server database. This document serves as a notice about what data is collected, what part of it is public/visible to admins and how it is handled.  
_\* For new updates / iterations on our server we use an incremental number, like server3, server4, etc._

### Consent

By registering an account or playing Beyond All Reason you consent to the terms stated in this Privacy Policy. If you have any concerns about how BAR is handling your User Personal Information, please let us know immediately at [\[email protected\]](https://www.beyondallreason.info/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection).

‍

### Information we collect

##### Visible publicly:

* Username
* User aliases used in the past on official battlerooms (history of renames)
* Country flag (based on IP address, possible to be hidden optionally)
* OpenSkill rating ([Read more](https://www.beyondallreason.info/guide/rating-and-lobby-balance))
* Player rank/level based on in-game time
* Chat logs from public lobby chat channels
* History of game matches played online in non-private battlerooms (including the full setup, results, in-game actions over time, and chat including in-game messages)

##### Non-public data, visible to accounts with sufficient privilages (admin):

* Email address
* IP address
* Game lobby client used
* Client hardware specification
* Login dates and a log of actions taken while being online
* History of moderator/administrator action concerning the account
* History of abuse reports (both filed and received by the user)
* Website logs (containing browser User-Agent strings, IP addresses and pages visited)

##### Not visible to anyone (stored as a one-way hashed representation):

* Password

‍

### How we use your information

The information we collect is necessary for the functionality of the following services:

* In-game lobby client with all its functionality
* Replay browser as seen at [https://beyondallreason.info/replays](https://beyondallreason.info/replays)
* Active battles viewer as seen at [https://beyondallreason.info/active-battles](https://beyondallreason.info/active-battles)
* Leaderboards as seen at [https://beyondallreason.info/leaderboards](https://beyondallreason.info/leaderboards)

The collected information is also used for moderation and analytical purposes, supporting the game development and tuning.

‍

### Deleting your information

You can request the deletion of your Personal Information by contacting us at [\[email protected\]](https://www.beyondallreason.info/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection).

‍

### Children Data Protection

We care about protection for children on the internet. We encourage parents and guardians to observe, participate in, and/or monitor and guide their online activity.

Beyond All Reason does not knowingly collect any Personal Identifiable Information from children under the age of 13. If you think that your child provided this kind of information on our website or servers, we strongly encourage you to contact us immediately and we will do our best efforts to promptly remove such information from our records.

‍

### Open source

The entire source code for this server is [available on Github](https://github.com/beyond-all-reason/teiserver).

‍

Beyond All Reason RTS

Nav
===

Information
===========

ARMADA FACTION
==============

CORTEX FACTION
==============

Development
===========

OTHER
=====

Beyond All Reason is powered by
